(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
全世界、激震！
The whole world is shaking!
あの超大作が
That epic masterpiece...
ついに
...is finally...
スクリーンへ！！
...coming to the big screen!!
タイムリミットは24時間
The time limit is 24 hours.
人類の希望は
The hope of humanity...
4人の『（ピー音）』に託された
...has been entrusted to 4 "(Beep)".
なんだ？ここは！？
What? What is this place!?
どうして…… こんなのひどいよ！
Why... this is so cruel!
私のことはもういい　先に行け！
Don't worry about me, go on ahead!
いろは～～～～～！！！
Iroha~~~~~!!!
あ、おふざけんな　待て！
Ah, don't mess around! Wait!
私たちの絆は　永遠！
Our bond is eternal!
みんなで人類を救うんだ！！
Together, we'll save humanity!!
絶対に忘れないよ……
I'll never forget...
自分史上、最高傑作です
It's my greatest masterpiece ever.
せーの　holoX4周年サイコー
Ready, set... holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
犯人は…… この中にいる！
The culprit is... among us!
えー！？　俺！？
Eh!? Me!?
これは……
This is...
背後から刀で一振り……
A single strike from behind with a sword...
探偵殿、どうしたでござるか？
Detective-dono, what's the matter?
怪しい
Suspicious.
殺人犯と一緒の場所にいられるか！　部屋に戻らせてもらう！
As if I can stay in the same place as a murderer! I'm going back to my room!
怪しい
Suspicious.
……ふふふふふふ
...fufufufufufu.
怪しい
Suspicious.
最初から最後まで　ハラハラドキドキでしたー
It was thrilling and heart-pounding from start to finish.
せーの　holoX4周年サイコー
Ready, set... holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
私の名前は博衣こより！　どこにでもいる普通の高校生！
My name is Hakui Koyori! Just an ordinary high school student you'd find anywhere!
ただ一つ人と違うことは　科学が好き……ってところかな？
The only thing different about me is that... I like science, I guess?
いっけなーい！遅刻遅刻ぅーーー
Oh no! I'm late, I'm late!
いったー
Ouch.
見つけた
Found you.
一緒にいると、なんか安心するでござる
When I'm with you, I somehow feel at ease.
いただきましよ！
I'll take it!
あ、ちょっと！
Ah, wait!
最悪！
The worst!
申し訳ありません
I am very sorry.
甘じょっぱさが絶妙でしたー
The bittersweetness was exquisite.
せーの　holoX4周年サイコー
Ready, set... holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
あ、あなた……！ holoX4周年を検索しちゃったんですか！！！
Ah, you...! Did you search for holoX 4th Anniversary!!!
決して、検索してはイケナイ　「#SSholoX4周年」
Never, ever search for "#SSholoX4thAnniversary".
※この動画は配信本編とは一切関係ありません。
*This video has nothing to do with the main stream.
ひとり... 検索し人...
One... person searching...
「SSholoX4周年」を検索した人間に降りかかる
Befalling those who searched for "#SSholoX4thAnniversary"
数々の出来事――
Numerous events—
ルイ姉...
Lui-nee...
いろは、大丈夫だから...
Iroha, it's okay...
いろは？
Iroha?
いろは！
Iroha!
ボア！
Bwaa!
（すごい悲鳴！）
(A huge scream!)
あーっ！
Aaah!
終始、鳥肌が立ちっぱなしでしたー
I had goosebumps the whole time!
せーの
Ready, go!
holoX4周年サイコー！
holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
La la pa pa pa, pa la la pa pa pa,
La la pa pa pa, pa la la pa pa pa...
迷宮なラビリンス
Meikyuu na Labyrinth
In this confusing labyrinth
ノー招かれた招待状
No uninvited invitations
秘密で酷な1次元マンション
A secret and cruel one-dimensional mansion
方々のあの子案に
Following that girl's plan everywhere
No pay, no game, archer
Get on out the hawk eye
迫る白亜はWar cry
The approaching chalk is a war cry
奔走自在に突破口も
Struggling freely for a breakthrough
堂々巡りの走馬灯
A revolving lantern of endless circles
Xに撮り込まれていくよ
Being captured into the X
刻印刻まれ
The seal is engraved
不条理めいた脱出案
An absurd plan for escape
ドワカタ ドワイリョウジョ
Bewared the door, beware the girl
さあ 研ぎ澄ませよピュア
Now, sharpen your purity
響け笑い声
Let the laughter ring out
La la pa pa pa, pa la la pa pa pa,
La la pa pa pa, pa la la pa pa pa...
ド真ん中反転
Reversal at the dead center
力こそパワー
Might is power
素敵な迷宮のラビリンス せーの
The wonderful meikyuu labyrinth, ready, go!
ラビリンス 突き進め
Push forward through the labyrinth
迷い無き勇気
An unwavering courage
強固で不屈なWi-Fi
Strong and unyielding Wi-Fi
これマジで最強ルームだけど
This is seriously the strongest room, but
方々の回路は普通に
The circuits everywhere are normally
危ない
Dangerous
One shot, one kill
現実踊るマリオネット
A marionette dancing in reality
落ちる部屋はダンジョン
The room you fall into is a dungeon
ランク外は眼中にないが
Those out of rank aren't even worth considering
楽マイ 赤んくなる
Easy my, it's turning red
Xに撮り込まれていく
Being captured into the X
迷える子羊君たち
You lost little lambs
お砂糖スパイス それと
Sugar, spice, and
ピンクな4周年で
with a pink 4th anniversary,
ハイになれるドリンクできたよ
I made a drink that'll get you high!
毒味飲んでくださいね
Please have a taste of the poison
holoX 捧げに
to offer up to holoX
（笑い声）
(Laughing)
さあさあ皆様のうめ手ござれ
わが世の春
Now then, everyone, come and see the spectacle
of my prime in this world
いや、お前が飲むんかい
じゃあ とりあえず
Wait, you're the one drinking it?!
Well, for now...
乾杯！
Cheers!
鏡の街道から
From the mirrored highway
抵抗の熱唱警報
A resistance singing warning
塗り替えられる情夜
A night of emotion being rewritten
見果てろ笑い声
See the end of the laughter
お前たちもな！
You guys too!
La la pa pa pa, pa la la pa pa pa,
La la pa pa pa, pa la la pa pa pa...
立ち止まれ 5人の元
Stop where the five of us are
重なって声を高らかに
Loudly raising our voices together
ラパパ ラララパパ
Rapapa rararapapa
底なしの海を超えるため
To cross the bottomless sea
強気本点 不屈が痛い
Determined headquarters, indomitability is painful
投げ飛ばせ 最高の
Throw it away, the best...
スーパーフューチャー パーティーラビリンス
Super Future Party Labyrinth
バイバーイ
Bye-bye!
ということで！
And so!
はい！
Yes!
holoX 4周年！
holoX 4th Anniversary!
イェーイ！おめでとう！
Yay! Congratulations!
おめでとう！ありがとう！
Congratulations! Thank you!
よし、みんな、張り切っていくぞー！
Alright everyone, let's give it our all!
オー！
Oh!
じゃあちょっとね、これからの活動の抱負を...
Well then, let's share our aspirations for future activities...
早いね、テンポ！
That was a quick transition!
早いね！
So fast!
私から！
I'll start!
私から？
From me?
聞いてないよ！私から？
I didn't hear about this! Me first?
どうしようかな...
What should I say...
えーっと、みんなありがとう！
Umm, thank you everyone!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
えーっと、どうしようかな... 5年目も...
Umm, let's see... In our 5th year as well...
頑張るぞ！holoX頑張るぞ！
We'll do our best! holoX will do our best!
イェーイ！おー！やったー！
Yay! Oh! Hooray!
はい、じゃあ、こより！
Okay, next, Koyori!
はい！
Yes!
えー、この5年目は、4人でもっと団結力をグッと...
Uh, in this 5th year, the four of us will strengthen our unity even more...
ガッと！ガッ、ガッと！
Firmly! Firm, firmly!
そろそろ日本征服ぐらいはしていきたいなと...
I'd like us to at least achieve national conquest soon...
確かに！日本ね！
True! Japan, right!
5年目の区切りというところで...
As a milestone in our 5th year...
世界はまだちょっと難しいけど...
The world might be a bit difficult still...
日本征服頑張ります！
We'll work hard for national conquest!
頑張るぞー！
Let's do our best!
ドロドロで行くぞ！はい、いろはー！
Let's go all out! Okay, Iroha!
はい！皆さん、ご、ご、ござるの5！
Yes! Everyone, fi, fi, five of 'gozaru'!
ということで、5年目もね...
And so, in our 5th year too...
元気に健やかに健康に活動頑張っていきたいと思いまーす！
I want to work hard and stay healthy and energetic in our activities!
holoX、5周年... 5年目頑張るぞ！
holoX, 5th anniversary... No, we'll do our best in our 5th year!
おー！頑張るぞ！5周年まで頑張ろう、また！
Oh! Let's do it! Let's work hard until our 5th anniversary!
そうだね！はい！
That's right! Yes!
じゃあ総帥！
Now, leader!
今年も生き残るぞ！
We'll survive this year too!
毎年言ってるよね！
You say that every year!
でも生き残れた、今年も！
But we survived this year too!
偉いぞ！そして！
Great job! And!
来年こそ！
Next year for sure!
5年目こそ！
Our 5th year for sure!
我らの年にするぞ！
We'll make it our year!
おー！するぞー！
Oh! We will!
ちょっと脱法... 待って、脱法すぎる！
A bit too much... Wait, that's way too much!
なんでなんで？同じ奴やってんの！
Why? Why? I'm doing the same thing!
おい、みんな同じ... こよりのダサさはどうでもいいです！
Hey, everyone is... Never mind Koyori's lameness!
はい、ちょっとみんな見てくださいよ！
Hey, everyone, please look at this!
ほら！ライブステージ！
Look! The live stage!
すごーい！かっこよくない？
Amazing! Isn't it cool?
holoXのさ、最初の登場からさ、うちらかっこよかったでしょ！
From holoX's first appearance, we were cool, right?
かっこよかったでしょ！
We were cool!
やめてね！
Stop it!
しかもですね、このステージ、ただ広いだけじゃなくて...
Moreover, this stage isn't just spacious...
色んな仕掛けがありますので！
It has various gimmicks!
な、何だって！？
Wh-What!?
何かの何か... 注目して！何かね、出てきたりとか！
Something something... Watch closely! Something will, like, come out!
出てきたり、出てきたり...
Coming out, coming out...
耳入る？耳はもう入ってる！
Will ears go in? Ears are already in!
そして上がったり！
And going up!
え、しっぽが上がってるぞ！？
Eh, the tail is going up!?
何、何、何？あのさ、変形したりとかさ...
What, what, what? You know, like transforming...
合体とか！
Or combining!
さすがに無理だろ！
That's surely impossible!
合体したい！合体したい！
I want to combine! I want to combine!
できました、こよりさん？
Was it possible, Koyori-san?
あるんじゃないの？合体は...
Isn't it there? The combination...
やりたかったんですけど！
I wanted to do it, but!
ちょっとさすがに、holoX予算が少なく...
Unfortunately, holoX's budget is a bit low...
当たり前じゃない！
Of course it is!
うちらの給料もっと上げてもいいよね！
They could raise our salaries more, right!
でもこのステージできたからいいじゃん！
But we got this stage, so it's fine!
ということで、5年目もholoXの皆さん、ぜひ...
And so, in our 5th year, everyone in holoX, please...
こんな我らですがよろしくお願いします！
Please take care of us, even though we're like this!
よろしくお願いします！
Please take care of us!
ちなみに、ここでお知らせでございます！
By the way, we have an announcement here!
ホロライブ公式チャンネルのメンバーシップに入ると...
If you join the Hololive official channel membership...
なんと限定絵文字スタンプが使えるようになりますので...
You'll be able to use exclusive emoji stamps...
ぜひコメントで使って盛り上げてください！
So please use them in the comments and get excited!
さらに！なんと今日からもう1つメンバーシップ特典があるらしく...
Furthermore! Starting today, there's apparently another membership perk...
先日発表した新曲「スキデカ」と「プライベートアイズ」の...
The wallpapers for our new songs 'Sukideka' and 'Private Eyes'...
壁紙ももらえちゃいます！
You can also get the wallpapers!
マジで！？うちらも入らなきゃいけないのかも...
Seriously!? Maybe we should join too...
ちょっと！
Hey!
holoX！4周年！
holoX! 4th Anniversary!
はい、そして本日は何やらライブだけではなく…
Yes, and today, it seems there's more than just the live...
お？
Oh?
重要な情報が…
Some important information...
重要？
Important?
もりもりもりもり、盛りだくさんらしいので！
It seems there's heaps and heaps of it!
盛りだくさん！盛りだくさん！
Lots of things! Lots of things!
皆さん、最後までちゃんと見ていくように！
Everyone, make sure to watch until the end!
見て！見て！
Watch! Watch!
途中退室禁止です！よろしくお願いします！
Leaving early is forbidden! Please stay tuned!
もり、もり、盛りだくさん…
Heaps and heaps of it...
あ、い、う、え、お！もりもり…
A, I, U, E, O! Mori mori...
ちょっと待ってください。なになん？なになん？
Wait a minute. What's going on? What's going on?
もう早くしないと。
We have to hurry.
みんなに見せられないから、ライブ。
We won't be able to show the live to everyone.
はい、早速！最初は…（ドラムロール）誰だ誰だ…
Okay, first up! The first one is... Who is it?
はい！こよりちゃんのパートから！
Yes! Starting with Koyori-chan's part!
イェーイ！
Yay!
なんだそのポーズ？キュート！可愛い！
What's that pose? Cute! So cute!
あ、可愛い！
Ah, so cute!
こよりちゃん行ってらっしゃい！バイバイ！
Koyori-chan, have a good one! Bye bye!
見ててね！見てるよ！
Watch me! We're watching!
頑張れ！走って！広いから！
Good luck! Run! It's a big stage!
急かさないでよ！
Don't rush me!
あ、邪魔だから行くよ。
Ah, you're in the way, so let's go.
え？俺たちも？
Eh? Us too?
早く！早く！行くぜ早く！
Hurry! Hurry! Let's go, hurry!
爆ラブ☆ケミストリー
作詞・作曲・編曲：ナユタン星人
Baku Love Chemistry
Lyrics, Music & Arrangement: Nayutalien
ラヴは必勝 存在実体マジ感 調合は未完成 トキメキのケミカ
Love is a sure win, the actual existence is imminent,
the compounding is incomplete, the chemistry of heartbeats
ふうんなるほど そんじゃこれならどうか 頓心ゲボならラブラトリー
Hmm, I see. Then how about this?
If it's the heart-moving type, then it's a love-ratory
はい！ハワあわててコーション 待てる花には甘いなるなる
Yes! Flustered, flustered, caution!
The flowers that wait will become sweet
はい！シュ集中感情のモーション 奇跡的に美味しくなーれ
Yes! Con-concentrated emotional motion,
let it become miraculously delicious!
フラスコにハート やべなってアート 効果のテスト 君が一番
Hearts in the flask, oh no, it's an art,
testing the effects, you are the best
こら僕は君になれ ちょっと危険なまぜまぜ
Hey, I want to become you,
a slightly dangerous mixing
ドッカン！ケミストリーなの 曖昧な君クロマトグラフィー
Bang! It's chemistry,
chromatography of the ambiguous you
へ・わ・こ・いのジェネリック もっと中になれなーさ
He-wa-ko-i's generic,
become more addicted
はい！ハイ！もっと化成 キュって止めたい君の胸
Yes! Hi! More reaction,
I want to stop your heart tight
あ・ま・さに振幅フラスコ 爆誕君とケミストリー
S-s-sweetness amplitude flask,
birth of chemistry with you
再・爆の甘いエジェ 溶けるくないドキドキするはず
The sweet agent of re-explosion,
it won't melt, your heart should throb
め・白い煙吐いて そっちのタイプのドキドキじゃない
S-spitting out white smoke,
it's not that type of throb
けどまあある意味成功かな？
But well, in a way, is it a success?
ラヴは不要成 日記を持って無し感 調合は試作中 噛んだのは飛べさ
Love is an unnecessary addition, keeping a diary is a no-no,
compounding is in trial, the thing I bit was to fly away
ゆ・どこ行く？そんなトライ検爆発 君と重ねてクてるテテテ
Wh-where are you going? Such a trial explosion,
overlapping with you, kuteru-te-te-te
キュッと冷めさせたくて二の恥 ラブ瓶に眠る君が一番
Wanting to cool it down quickly, the second shame,
you sleeping in the love-vial are the best
中・さ・さ・い加・で・す・か バクバク君のアンチドート
Wh-wh-what do you think of the small bit of chemistry,
the thumping antidote for you
ドッカン！ケミストリーなの 曖昧な君クロマトグラフィー
Bang! It's chemistry,
chromatography of the ambiguous you
へ・わ・こ・いのジェネリック どんな毒も観測してさ
He-wa-ko-i's generic,
observing any kind of poison
ドッカン！君プラスハート ケモすぎて三十シナジー
Bang! You plus heart,
too much chemistry, triple synergy
み・み・こ・そ・が愛のアトミック もっと中になれなーさ
Th-th-this is the atomic of love,
become more addicted
はい！ハイ！もっと化成 キュって止めたい君の胸
Yes! Hi! More reaction,
I want to stop your heart tight
あ・ま・さに振幅フラスコ 爆誕君と追加検証
S-s-sweetness amplitude flask,
birth of further verification with you
はい！ハイ！もっと化成 ギュってしてよ僕の胸
Yes! Hi! More reaction,
squeeze my chest
あ・ま・さに振幅フラスコ 爆誕君とケミストリー
S-s-sweetness amplitude flask,
birth of chemistry with you
実験は君とエターナリー
Experimenting eternally with you
君が好きってこの感情に潰されてる
I like you, I'm being crushed by this emotion
足りないのはどちらのほうか どうでもいいかも
It might not matter which one of us is lacking
興味ないよ
作詞・作曲・編曲：jon-YAKITORY
Kyouryuu nai yo
Lyrics, Music & Arrangement: jon-YAKITORY
気づいたって知らないよね 責任のって
Even if you notice, you won't care, take responsibility
私は何で好きなんだって　問い正さなきゃね
I have to ask myself why I like you so much.
最低なあなた　あの子の方がいいんだもんね
You're the worst. That girl is better for you anyway.
私興味ないよ　君なんて　中途半端に舐めた真似
I'm not interested in you, making half-hearted, mocking attempts.
ロックでビッチなこの愛に　壊されないでいい
You don't have to be destroyed by this rock 'n' roll, bitchy love.
止めどないよ　君の愛を独り占めしたい
It's unstoppable. I want to monopolize your love.
特攻だろうがなんだろうが　抱きしめてあげたい
Whether it's a suicide mission or whatever, I want to hold you tight.
来世契約　独占のホリデイズ　逃がさないずっと
A contract for the next life, exclusive holidays. I'll never let you go.
君が好きってこの感情に　騙されてる
I'm being deceived by this feeling of "liking you."
大事な方は君か　確か決めかねてる
I haven't decided if you're the important one.
私興味ないよ　君なんて　ただ振り回して好きなだけ
I'm not interested in you. I just like to boss you around.
ロックでビップなこの愛を　渡さないから
I won't give away this rock 'n' roll, VIP love.
馬鹿だよね　色ボケだね　それ見たことかだってさ
You're a fool, aren't you? Blinded by love. "I told you so," they'll say.
もう他でもない　あなたに呪われたまま
No one else but you has me under a spell.
私興味ないよ　君なんて　馬鹿なフリしてあげただけ
I'm not interested in you. I was just playing dumb.
愛と哀をぶつけ合って　ぐちゃぐちゃになって
Clashing love and sorrow until it's all a mess.
私興味ないよ　君なんて　中途半端に舐めた真似
I'm not interested in you, making half-hearted, mocking attempts.
ロックでビッチなこの愛に　壊されないでいい
You don't have to be destroyed by this rock 'n' roll, bitchy love.
見た目だけじゃわからない　私のこと可愛いだなんて
You can't tell just by looks. Thinking I'm cute...
まさか思っていないよね？　私の本当を知っていてほしい
You don't actually think that, do you? I want you to know the real me.
ホントノワタシ
The Real Me
やっと覚悟したの　反動不足も事態も問わない
I've finally made up my mind. I don't care about the backlash or the situation.
おすまし顔でいるけど　心は常に蒼白く燃え
I keep a composed face, but my heart is always burning pale blue.
諦めはしない　媚びたりもしない　私負けない
I won't give up. I won't flatter anyone. I won't lose.
扱いづらい奴だとも　甘く見ると痛い目見るぞ
Even if I'm hard to handle, if you underestimate me, you'll regret it.
それでも時々には　逃げ出してしまいたい
Even so, sometimes I want to run away.
そんな衝動に弱音吐き出す　夜もある
There are nights when I give in to those impulses and voice my weaknesses.
ほんの小さな小さな妥協が　積み重なり重なって動けない
Slight, tiny compromises pile up until I can't move.
大きな大きな我を通し　未来を狭めてしまうから
If I force my big, stubborn ego, it will narrow my future.
どんなに苦しくても辛くても　後悔だけはしない
No matter how painful or hard it is, I won't have any regrets.
生き方の重荷さ　建前じゃなくて生き方なんだ
It's the burden of my way of life. It's not a pretense, it's how I live.
現実と理想の距離を　縮められなかったとしても
Even if I couldn't bridge the gap between reality and my ideals.
おすまし顔でいるだけ　何事もなかったかのように
I just keep a composed face, as if nothing happened.
立ち止まりはしない　後戻りもしない　夢を捨てない
I won't stop. I won't go back. I won't give up on my dreams.
私らしくとか　らしくとか...
Being myself, or like myself...
いいなんて決めつけないで
Don't just decide that it's "good"
全部私
It's all me
それでも時には　温もりが恋しい
Even so, sometimes I long for warmth
そんな感情に流されてしまいそうな夜もある
There are nights when I feel like I'm about to be swept away by such emotions
こんな甘い甘い言葉だけ
Just these sweet, sweet words
求めてしまうような弱さじゃない
It's not a weakness that just seeks those
二回、三回、経験だって
Two times, three times, even experiences
私を強くしてくれたから
Have made me stronger
これが　これが私の
This is, this is my
本当
Truth
とても狭い狭い世界の中からだけでは
Just from within this very narrow, narrow world
笑わねんだ
I won't laugh
広い広い世界の果てまで
To the ends of the vast, vast world
駆け抜けて生きていくんだから
Because I'm going to run through and live my life
どんなに苦しくて　残酷でも
No matter how painful or cruel it is
楽しんでやるさ
I'll enjoy it
いけてる桃色めちゃめちゃじゃなくて
It's not about being a cool pink mess
生き方なんだから
It's about my way of life
アナスタシスガール feat. ラプラス・ダークネス
Anastasis Girl feat. La+ Darknesss
ハイ　注目
Hey, attention!
あれもこれもそれもタブー
That, this, and that too are all taboo
分かってんの？　待って頂戴
Do you understand? Please wait
マスターバース　ガチャガチャ邪魔すんぞ
Masterverse, I'm gonna mess things up noisily
分かってんの？　ストップしなさい
Do you understand? Stop it
ここがベスト　凝視しな　パースト　ベベベ邪魔じゃない？　邪魔じゃない？　デクノボウ
This is the best, stare at it. Burst. Isn't it annoying? Isn't it annoying? You blockhead
表面だけ追って　剥落してもね
Even if you just follow the surface and it peels off...
痛いの　痛いの　飛んで行けないくらい
It hurts, it hurts, so much I can't fly away
称賛　悪化　細胞　脳内高鳴り出しましょう
Praise, deterioration, cells. Let's bring out the thumping in our brains
あたし　アナスタシスガール　不滅強さが漲る
I'm an Anastasis Girl, immortal strength overflows
だから　ラララララ　1、2の3で　ダンダンダン
So, la la la la la, on the count of 1, 2, 3, bang bang bang
アナスタシスガール　昨日いじめた罰
Anastasis Girl, the punishment for bullying yesterday
君は　ラララララ　地獄へ　ダンダンダン
You're going to hell, la la la la la, bang bang bang
革命御来
Revolution's coming
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl
口寂　弱
Lonely mouth, silence
皆ね　ハナイチモンジ
Everyone, Hanaichimonji
口寂　弱
Lonely mouth, silence
あたしだけに囁け
Whisper only to me
健やかなる時も　病める時も
In sickness and in health
全開　限界　人間らしくあれ
Full throttle, limit, be human-like
共鳴　微調整が不味いだけ
Resonance, it's just that the fine-tuning is bad
体温　体温　体温　体温
Body temperature, temperature, temperature, temperature
体温　体温　体温
Body temperature, temperature, temperature
痛いの　痛いの　飛んでいけないならば
It hurts, it hurts, if I can't fly away
やっちゃいな　生死を　選んで　目には目を　満たしてやりましょう
Do it, choose life or death, an eye for an eye, let's satisfy it
あたし　アナスタシスガール　ブレイク　鼓動の時間
I'm an Anastasis Girl, break, the time of heartbeat
だから　ラララララ　1、2の3で　ダンダンダン
So, la la la la la, on the count of 1, 2, 3, bang bang bang
アナスタシスガール　極めて遺憾です
Anastasis Girl, it's extremely regrettable
君は　ラララララ　地獄へ　ダンダンダン
You're going to hell, la la la la la, bang bang bang
革命御来
Revolution's coming
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl
ああ　お願い　放っといて
Ah, please leave me alone
閉じ込め　閉鎖　接触　嘘も飛び散る　追走　停止　邪魔すんぞ
Locked up, closed, contact, lies scattering too. Tracking, stop, I'm gonna mess things up
汚れたらその肌　生み出した時　奪って
When it gets dirty, that skin, I'll take it at the moment of its birth
あたし　アナスタシスガール　不滅強さが漲る
I'm an Anastasis Girl, immortal strength overflows
だから　ラララララ　1、2の3で　ダンダンダン
So, la la la la la, on the count of 1, 2, 3, bang bang bang
アナスタシスガール　昨日いじめた罰
Anastasis Girl, the punishment for bullying yesterday
君は　ラララララ　地獄へ　ダンダンダン
You're going to hell, la la la la la, bang bang bang
革命御来
Revolution's coming
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl
好きじゃない 好きじゃない ああ
I don't love you, I don't love you, ah
ラブのリポート 冷めやがぬ感情
A report of love, feelings that won't cool down
馬鹿じゃないの 目を覚ましてね
Aren't you a fool? Please wake up
全然平常心で 興味と過信だらけ
With total composure, full of interest and overconfidence
さらけ出して Want you
Expose yourself, want you
自覚できなくて困る
It's a problem I can't realize it
たまたまに構ってあげる
I'll give you some attention once in a while
癖になっちまう絶妙な距離感
This perfect distance is becoming a habit
ゲーム 近く近付く
The game gets closer and closer
一緒 デカく デカく デカく
Together, big, big, big
何でも頂戴 サイズ出す 好き作りましょう
Give me anything, show the size, let's make some love
それがライクなのか ラブなのか
Is that like or is that love?
はたまた両方なんでば
Or perhaps it's both?
なし あり なし 絶対ありだろ
No, yes, no, it's definitely yes!
そして デカく デカく デカく
And then, big, big, big
いよいよ全部叶うからね
Finally, everything will come true
結局 重い内と 重い内と
In the end, while it's heavy, while it's heavy...
対処やっていきましょう
Let's deal with it
一緒 デカく 好き デカく
Together, big, love, big
しばらくお付き合いよろしくな
Look forward to our time together for a while
スキデカ スキデカ
Suki-deka, suki-deka
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
たくさんの感情 みんなに伝えて
Tell everyone about all these emotions
俺だけに 見せてくれたっていいぜ いいぜ
It's okay to show them only to me
一人と特別サービスはできません
I can't give special service to just one person
それでもいいかな
Is that okay nonetheless?
もっと知りたいことだらけ ほどほどにして
So many things I want to know, keep it in moderation
でも知らないほうが幸せか どっちかにしてよね
But is ignorance bliss? Choose one or the other
絶妙な距離感 ゲームバランス取り合う
Perfect distance, balancing the game with each other
一緒 付かず離れずは 辛いから ちょうど良く按配で
Being neither too close nor too far is hard, so just the right balance
お互いもっと解り合えたら 特別になれる
If we can understand each other more, we can become special
そうだ いつも通じ合える
That's right, we can always communicate
この先は想像できないけど 結構いい感じかも
I can't imagine the future, but it might feel pretty good
ギリギリでもいいから そのまま進みます
Even if it's just barely, I'll keep going like this
踏み付けていきましょう
Let's step forward
ここで今後の我々について話し合っていきたい
I want to discuss our future here
今は要らないでしょ！
We don't need that now!
いいからほら！
Just do it!
3, 2, 1, Let's go!
一緒 すれ違う二人で
Together, two people passing each other
一緒 デカく デカく デカく
Together, big, big, big
何でも頂戴 サイズ出す 好き作りましょう
Give me anything, show the size, let's make some love
それがライクなのか ラブなのか
Is that like or is that love?
はたまた両方なんでば
Or perhaps it's both?
なし あり なし 絶対ありだろ
No, yes, no, it's definitely yes!
そして デカく デカく デカく
And then, big, big, big
デカく デカく いよいよ全部叶うからね
Big, big, finally everything will come true
結局 重い内と 重い内と
In the end, while it's heavy, while it's heavy...
対処やっていきましょう
Let's deal with it
一緒 付かず離れず 呆れず
Together, neither too close nor too far, without getting fed up
ちょうど良く按配で
Just the right balance
お前ともっと くだらないことでも 笑っていたい
I want to laugh with you more, even over trivial things
感情 付き合っていたい
I want to keep sharing these emotions
この先も 変わらない関係性を
A relationship that won't change in the future
ちょっと行き過ぎて またちょっと深呼吸
Going a bit too far, then another deep breath
一先ず進みます
For now, I'll keep going
好き
Love
さっさと戻ります
I'll go back quickly
なんでだよ！
Why?!
好きは デカく 好き デカく
Love is big, love is big
しばらくお付き合いよろしくな
Look forward to our time together for a while
不思議な関係 お見知りおきを
Please take note of this mysterious relationship
超常現象 Phenomenon 東奔西走 Timeless
Supernatural phenomenon, phenomenon, busying about everywhere, timeless
The Red One
最強
Strongest
今 焼き付けろ
Burn it into your mind now
超常現象 Phenomenon 東奔西走 Timeless
Supernatural phenomenon, phenomenon, busying about everywhere, timeless
我ら 目指して
Aim for us
煌めいて
And sparkle
バッバッバッバ
Ba ba ba ba
満月の夜 潜り抜けて
Passing through the night of the full moon
ヴェールの隙間まで溜息を
A sigh into the gap of the veil
Wow...
本線のルートで 探し出して
Searching through the main route
深海 闇へ 囁う
Whispering to the darkness of the deep sea
対包囲網 機密の調査
Anti-siege investigation, secret investigation
有言実行 世界を制や
Keeping my word, conquering the world
オレンジに染まっていく崩壊
Collapsing into a shade of orange
さよなら
Goodbye
君のために ヴェラメーラ
For you, Veramera
愛を燃やして ヴェラメーラ
Burning with love, Veramera
守り抜くと誓ったあの日から
From the day I vowed to protect you
明日のために ヴェラメーラ
For tomorrow, Veramera
炎とに乗っちゃえば
If you ride with the flames
退屈なんて Endless さよなら
Boredom is endless, goodbye
Wow...
超常現象 Phenomenon 東奔西走 Timeless
Supernatural phenomenon, phenomenon, busying about everywhere, timeless
The Red One
最強
Strongest
今 焼き付けろ
Burn it into your mind now
超常現象 Phenomenon 東奔西走 Timeless
Supernatural phenomenon, phenomenon, busying about everywhere, timeless
我ら 目指して
Aim for us
煌めいて
And sparkle
バッバッバッバ
Ba ba ba ba
栄光が照らす 欲望の影を
Glory shines on the shadows of desire
忍び合わせて 欺いて
Sneaking along, deceiving
Wow...
震えてる手を 握り締めよう
Let's hold tight to our trembling hands
...the same 譲れない場所
...the same, a place I won't yield
変化カモフラージュ迷彩カメレオン
Change, camouflage, stealthy chameleon
忠義ラッシャイ甘味チョコレート
Loyalty welcome! Sweet chocolate
エセ理路整然起きる副作用
Pseudo-logic, side effects occurring
夢のためにメラメラ
Burning bright for the sake of dreams
闇を燃やせメラメラ
Burn the darkness, blazing hot
どんな時もこの声を届けたい
No matter the time, I want to deliver this voice
崖っぷちでメラメラ
Blazing at the edge of the cliff
諦めるには早いわ
It's too early to give up
因果応報 奇跡のおまじない
Karma, a miracle spell
マスタピースクラス参詣 玲瓏天然記念年
Masterpiece class pilgrimage, an exquisite natural monument year
純真誠意 意外です生涯たってお真面目
Purity and sincerity, surprising, serious throughout my life
どこにいたって迷子になっちゃってもブンブンス
Wherever I am, even if I get lost, I'll keep on buzzing
有象無象全部無理やりまいて
Shaking off all the riff-raff by force
電光石火 追い付け！
Lightning speed, catch up!
君のためにメラメラ
Blazing for your sake
愛を燃やせメラメラ
Burn with love, blazing hot
守り抜くと誓ったあの日から
From the day I swore to protect everything
明日のためにメラメラ
Burning for the sake of tomorrow
この音に乗って目指せ
Aim ahead, riding on this sound
退屈なんて無縁でしょ さようなら
Boredom is irrelevant, so goodbye
超常現象 フェノメノピックアップ 専横 奔走 タイムレプス
Paranormal phenomenon pickup, arbitrary dash, time-lapse
オレトッカ コノサイキョーカ イマヤキツケロ
Specialize me, this power-up, sear it in now
超常現象 フェノメノピックアップ 専横 奔走 タイムレプス
Paranormal phenomenon pickup, arbitrary dash, time-lapse
マネメタ ヤマメタ パンパッパッパッパン
Money-meta, Yama-meta, bang-bang-bang-bang-bang
ね、ね、ね！総帥、めっちゃ良かったね！
Hey, hey, hey! Leader, that was amazing!
めっちゃ良かったね！
It was great!
めっちゃ楽しいね！
It's so much fun!
マジ神ゲー！
Seriously the best!
あの、めっちゃいいよね！
Um, it's really good, right!
まだ終わってないけど、まだ終わってないよ！
It's not over yet, it's not over!
これからも最高だよね！
It'll be the best from here on too, right!
なにこれ？なになにこれ？
What's this? What, what's this?
お？あ？
Oh? Ah?
気づいちゃいました？
Did you notice?
まじ分かりだ。てかカッコよくない？めっちゃカッコいいじゃん。
It's so obvious. Wait, isn't it cool? It's really cool.
こよりが作りました！
Koyori made these!
また！また経費使ったんか！
Again! Did you use the expenses again?!
これがござるの給料を...
This is from Gozaru's salary...
アピール早！
Promotion already?!
いやいやいや、清掃...これがなかろうが給料は同じだからね！
No, no, no, cleaning... even if this wasn't here, the salary would be the same!
なにこれ？
What is this?
ということで、これは告知用カードを持ってきました！
And so, I've brought out the announcement cards!
告知！
Announcement!
ということで、この流れでグッズ紹介でございますね！
So, following this, we have the goods introduction!
イェーイ！
Yay!
今回はそういう感じね！
So it's like that this time!
はい、ということで... はい、じゃあ私からね、行きますよ！
Yes, and so... Okay, I'll go first!
はい！holoX活動4周年記念グッズ「Secret Society holoX Anniversary Parade」、今日の18時より販売開始されております！
Yes! holoX 4th Anniversary Goods "Secret Society holoX Anniversary Parade" are on sale starting from 18:00 today!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
それではそれぞれ見ていきましょう。まずはプレミアムアクリル色紙！ドン！
Now let's look at each one. First, the premium acrylic board! Bam!
イェーイ！
Yay!
今回のキービジュアルを使用したアクリル色紙です。なんと複製サインとロゴが箔押しになっててめっちゃいい感じです！
This is an acrylic board using the key visual. It has reproduced signatures and the logo is foil-stamped, it looks really nice!
カッコいい！
So cool!
そして、お次がこちら。ホロカスリーブ！このカードがまさにそれなんですけど...
Next is this. The Holoca sleeve! This card is exactly that...
キービジュアルを使ったホロカスリーブです。こちらなんと60枚入り！
It's a Holoca sleeve using the key visual. This contains 60 sleeves!
わお！やったぜ！
Wow! We did it!
何枚あってもいいですからね！
You can never have too many!
ホロカに使いやすいですね！
It's easy to use for Holoca!
そして...
And...
はい！元気だな。アクリルスタンド！
Yes! Energetic. Acrylic stands!
おおー！可愛い！
Whoa! Cute!
キービジュアルのデザインの表情違いになってるんで、ぜひアクリル色紙と比べてみてくださいね！
These have different expressions from the key visual design, so please compare them with the acrylic board!
気持ちわる...
Gross...
帰ってきた、帰ってきた！
I'm back, I'm back!
こよりと、いろはも可愛いね！
Koyo and Iroha are cute too!
えっちだな。
Sexy.
そしてこちら！はい、記念メダルも発売しております！
And this! Yes, the commemorative medals are also on sale!
なんとケースと巾着がついてくる記念メダルでございます。こちら期生ごとでデザインが異なっておりますので...
These are commemorative medals that come with a case and a drawstring bag. The design differs for each generation...
なんと今回はholoXだけのデザインになっております。ぜひぜひゲットしてよくチェックしてみてね。
And this time it's a holoX-exclusive design. Please get yours and check it out.
なんか騒がしいな。騒がしいです。そのドリルやめろ、そのドリルやめろ！
It's getting noisy. It's noisy. Stop that drill, stop that drill!
はい、ということで、次は何のカードかな？カードちゃん、オープン！
Okay, what's the next card? Card-chan, open!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ということで、タイミーコラボ！
And so, the Timee collaboration!
タイミーだ！タイミー！
Timee! Timee!
やっていましたね！先日のタイミーで募集したレアバイトなんですけど、現地の様子があるということで...
We did it! This is the rare part-time job we recruited for on Timee the other day, and we have footage from the site...
ビデオ見てみましょう！どうぞ、ドン！
Let's watch the video! Here you go, bam!
おおー！すごい！ホロクサーたちだ！
Ooh! Amazing! It's the holoXers!
すごい！ホロクサーしてる！すげー！持ってる持ってる！
Amazing! They're totally holoXers! Wow! They're holding it!
ありがとうみんな！ありがとう！被られている！
Thank you everyone! Thank you! They're wearing them!
他にもありますよ。ドン！
There's more. Bam!
え？女の子？女の子！
Eh? A girl? A girl!
すごい、めっちゃ見られてる！めっちゃ見られてる！
Wow, people are really staring! They're really staring!
これでもう、本当にあんな風になるんだって...
I was like, 'Oh, it's actually going to be like that...'
これで知ってくれた人もいるよね、多分。
I'm sure some people found out about us through this.
ね、絶対そう！
Yeah, definitely!
もう一枚あります！ドーン！
There's one more! Boom!
おおー！えっ、新宿！？
Whoa! Wait, Shinjuku!?
待って待って、後ろにも映ってる！？
Wait, wait, are we on the screens in the back too!?
え、あれ聞いた！？
Eh, did you hear about that!?
聞いてない、嘘でしょ！？
I didn't hear anything, you're kidding me!?
待って、今日のあの21時前に流れていた、あのよく分からない映像...
Wait, that weird video that was playing before 9:00 PM today...
おい、流れてしまったのかよ！
Hey, did that actually air!?
大丈夫か？あれ、いいのかよ！
Is that okay? Is that really alright!?
もっとさ、かっこいいMVとか...
I thought we'd have like, a cool MV or something...
ライブ映像とか流したらもっと...
If we played live footage, it would be even more...
まあまあまあ、ありがたいね。
Well, well, it's still something to be grateful for.
ありがとー！
Thank you!
やったー！
We did it!
ということで、こちら！応募どれぐらい来たと思う？
So, here it is! How many applications do you think we got?
300人！でもお仕事だからね。
300 people! But since it's a job...
500人とか来てくれてるんじゃない？
Maybe around 500 people applied?
1000人とかじゃない？大変だからね。
Maybe 1000? It's tough work, after all.
なんと、数千人の応募が来たということです！
Believe it or not, we received several thousand applications!
すごすぎる！ありがとー！
That's incredible! Thank you!
驚きすぎた！
I'm so surprised!
うわああああ！
Waaaah!
誰か給料もらってるせいで！
It's because someone's getting paid!
いろはよりも多めに渡してます。
I'm giving them more than Iroha.
やめてー！しっかり福利厚生、ラプ様ですから！
Stop it! La-plus-sama provides solid benefits!
ありがとうございます！掃除係の皆もありがとー！
Thank you very much! And thanks to the cleaning crew too!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
そして、次はなんだ？
And what's next?
告知③ タイアップコラボ詳細決定！
Announcement 3: Tie-up Collaboration Details Finalized!
オープン！来い来い来い！
Open! Here it comes!
タワーコラボだー！
It's a tower collaboration!
俺がタワーになる！タ、タ、タワー！
I'll be the tower! T-T-Tower!
タワーコラボ、もう情報公開されていますが、こちら！
Information about the tower collab is already out, but look at this!
全国4箇所で行われる、holoX Tower Invasion！イエーイ！
Happening at four locations nationwide: holoX Tower Invasion! Yay!
12月4日から開催されます！
It starts on December 4th!
さっぽろテレビ塔、東京タワー、中部電力 MIRAI TOWER、梅田スカイビルで開催されます！
It'll be at Sapporo TV Tower, Tokyo Tower, Chubu Electric Power MIRAI TOWER, and Umeda Sky Building!
ぜひ皆さん、行ってくださいね！
Please make sure to go, everyone!
俺たちがholoX十タワーです！
We are the holoX Ten-Tower!
おい待て待て、今回大事なことがあるんですけど...
Hey, wait a minute, there's something important about this...
ちゃんと予約をしないと、皆さん入れないんで。事前予約必須です！
You can't get in without a reservation. Advanced booking is mandatory!
そうなんです。事前予約、忘れてる人もいると思うので。
That's right. I'm sure some people might forget about the pre-booking.
その場で行っても入れないらしいんで。
Apparently, you can't just show up and walk in.
皆さん、予約を忘れないように！
Everyone, don't forget to make your reservations!
よろしくお願いします！
We're counting on you!
次、次！
Next, next!
告知④ 4周年ライブブロマイド発売決定！
Announcement 4: 4th Anniversary Live Bromide Release!
オープン！はい！
Open! Yes!
なんと、ホロライブの新サービス、ライブの感動最速でお届け！
Believe it or not, Hololive's new service will deliver the excitement of the live show instantly!
おお、すごい！え、どういうこと？
Oh, wow! Wait, what do you mean?
秘密結社holoX、4周年のライブブロマイドが、なんと！
The Secret Society holoX 4th Anniversary Live Bromides, check this out!
今日のライブの写真が、明日からコンビニでプリントアウトできるんだって！
Photos from today's live will be available to print at convenience stores starting tomorrow!
すぐに手に入るんだ！
You can get them right away!
対象店舗は、ファミリーマート、ローソン、ミニストップになります！
The participating stores are FamilyMart, Lawson, and Ministop!
いっぱいあるね、ありがとうございます！
That's a lot of places. Thank you!
そして、今からネットで事前購入ができるらしいです！
And apparently, you can pre-purchase them online starting now!
マジ！？ただね、明日からコンビニでも写真を選びながら購入することもできるみたいなので。
Seriously!? Also, from tomorrow, you can choose and buy photos at the convenience stores too.
詳しくは、左下のリンクから確認してみてください！
For details, please check the link in the bottom left!
こっち、こっち！
Over here, over here!
さらにですね、今回はお写真にですね、ブロマイドに私たちのメッセージをつけることができるみたいなんですけど...
Furthermore, this time, we can apparently add our messages to the bromide photos...
え、いいの！？
Eh, is that okay!?
今から書く！？
Are we writing them now!?
ちょっと待って、急すぎないか！？
Wait a minute, isn't this too sudden!?
浮いてる、浮いてる！
They're floating, they're floating!
何も考えてないけど、まあ、考えて書いてください！
I haven't thought of anything, but please, think and write something!
はい！え、ちょ、待って...
Okay! Eh, wait, wait...
時間もね、迫ってますからね。早く書いて！
Time is running out, so write quickly!
にゃんにゃん。意外と集中力...
Nyan nyan. I'm actually focusing...
オッケー、書けたー！早い！
Okay, done! So fast!
待って、これ。見せて！
Wait, look at this. Show me!
あ、いい、こよっぽい。いつまで書いてんねん！
Ah, nice, that's so Koyo-like. How long are you going to take!
みんな終わった？回収、回収！
Is everyone done? Collect them, collect them!
画面に出して！お願いしますね。
Put them on the screen! Please.
みんな何書いたかすごく気になると思うんですが...
I'm sure everyone is curious about what we wrote...
メッセージの内容は、みんなが...私が書いたのは、あ、内緒！
The content of the messages is... what I wrote was, oh, it's a secret!
ダメですよ！言わないで！
You can't do that! Don't tell them!
買ってからのお楽しみ。ダメに決まってんだろ！
Wait until you buy them. Of course you can't say it now!
はい。そして...
Yes. And...
まだ2枚もあるんで、お次はこちら！
We still have two more left, so here's the next one!
告知⑤ 「あの作品とコラボ！？」
Announcement 5: "Collab with THAT work!?"
なんと、あの作品とコラボ！？え？
Wait, a collaboration with THAT work!? What?
なに、なに！？どれだ！？
What, what!? Which one is it!?
あの作品ってなんですか？こちらをどうぞ！
What is 'that work'? Take a look at this!
サテーー
Well then...
突然デハアルガ、
It's sudden, but...
或ル秘密結社ノ
Of a certain secret society's
人間ハ、話ヲシヨウ。
Humans, let's talk.
其ノ怪シイ集団ハ、
That mysterious group...
偶像ーー“アキドル”
Idols... "Akidol"
ナノダト云フ。
so they say.
ソシテーー
And then...
正確ナ話ヲスルト、
To tell the truth,
征服ショウトシテイルノハ
the one they're trying to conquer
エデンノ星ラシイ。
is apparently Planet Eden.
特別話　其ノ零
Special Story: Part Zero
コラボ開催決定
Collaboration decided!
えー！？ええ！？いいの！？
Eh?! What?! Is this okay?!
やばい！やばすぎる！
No way! This is crazy!
え、マジで？やばい！
Wait, seriously? Crazy!
え、え、すごすぎ！え、めっちゃ大好きじゃんね！
Eh, eh, it's amazing! I love this series so much!
ね！好き！
Right! I love it!
やばすぎる！どういうこと！？
Too crazy! What does this mean?!
え、やばすぎ！
Eh, way too crazy!
どこ行っちゃったの！？どこ行っちゃったの！？
Where did it go?! Where did it go?!
え、ちょっと！ありがとうございます！
Wait! Thank you so much!
なんと、マジで！え、怒られない我が輩！？
Seriously?! Wait, won't I get in trouble for this?!
怒られない！怒られない！
You won't! You won't!
怒られちゃったら、あの台本を読んでない子が怒られるから！
If anyone gets in trouble, it'll be the one who didn't read the script!
早く中身行こう！なんと、物語シリーズとのコラボが決定しました！
Let's check the details! A collaboration with the Monogatari Series has been decided!
どういうこと！？
What does that even mean?!
どういうこと！？って皆も言ってる！
Everyone in the chat is asking "What does that mean?!"
詳細は随時発表されるようなので、お楽しみに！
Details will be announced sequentially, so please look forward to it!
え、我々も分かっていない！？
Wait, we don't even know the details?!
そうなんです！本当に詳細が何も分かっていない！
That's right! We really don't know anything yet!
やばい！どういうことですか！？
Crazy! What's going on?!
えー、どうなるんでしょうか！？
Eh, I wonder how it'll turn out?!
いや、ちょっと、なんか、うちらもちょっとあの、焦ってるんですけど...
No, wait, we're actually a bit panicked too...
え、いいんですか？いいんですか？って感じなんですけれども。
We're feeling like, "Is this really okay? Is it fine?"
なんか、ちょっとね、あの、最後にもう一つあるみたいなので、そちらに行きましょう。
Anyway, it seems there's one last thing, so let's move on to that.
あ、もう一個！もう一個見ないといけないんで！
Ah, one more! We have to see one more thing!
ちょっと動揺、動揺...落ち着いてみんな。落ち着いて。
We're a bit agitated... everyone calm down. Calm down.
俺たちが動揺してる間に、皆さんこの6つ目が何なのか、コメントで教えてみてください！
While we're agitated, please try to guess what this 6th one is in the comments!
何かな？何かな？
What could it be?
予想して。予想して。
Make your predictions.
コメント見に行こう。
Let's check the comments.
おー、やばかったね。
Oh, that was crazy.
え、やば。
Eh, crazy.
え、何！？何！？ということで。
Eh, what?! What is it?! So...
最後の1つは皆さん何だと思われますか？
What do you all think the last one is?
なんとですね...まあちょっとヒントを言うと...
Well, the thing is... to give you a bit of a hint...
まあ、今年2曲作りましたよね？
Well, we made two songs this year, right?
あ、作ったじゃない。いっぱい出た。
Ah, we did. A lot of songs came out.
全部でholoXって何曲ありますか？
In total, how many songs does holoX have?
何曲だ？そして...
How many is it? And...
たくさん！
A lot!
覚えてないのか！？
You don't remember?!
holoXが出してきたあの企画を除きまして、全部で7曲あります！
Excluding those special projects, holoX has 7 songs in total!
7曲！？あー、すごい！多いね！
7 songs?! Oh, that's amazing! That's a lot!
え、ってことは？
Eh, which means?
もしや...皆わかってる？
Could it be... does everyone realize?
皆コメント欄分かってきたんじゃない！？
Everyone in the comments is starting to catch on, right?!
いや、あ、あ、分かってる分かってる分かってる！
No, wait, they know, they know, they know!
ということで、気づいてる人もいるみたいなので、やっぱりあちらでございます！
So, since it seems some people have noticed, it is indeed that one!
6枚目オープン！バン！
Let's open the 6th card! Bam!
なんと！ファーストアルバムが出ます！
What a surprise! Our first album is coming out!
やったー！
Yay!
嬉しい！ということで！ファーストアルバム「Secret ORDER」...
I'm so happy! So! Our first album, "Secret ORDER"...
じゃない、ファーストアルバム「Secret ORDER」！混ざった、混ざった。
Wait, our first album, "Secret ORDER"! I got my words mixed up.
大丈夫、大丈夫！シークレットオーダーだよ。
It's okay, it's okay! It's Secret ORDER.
はい、こちらの「Secret ORDER」、holoXでの4年間をぎゅっと詰め込んだアルバムとなっております！
Yes, this "Secret ORDER" is an album packed with our 4 years in holoX!
我々のデビュー曲「Joyful Paint」はオリジナルバージョンに加えて...
Our debut song "Joyful Paint," in addition to the original version...
本作のために新たにリアレンジされたバージョンも収録されています！
also features a newly rearranged version created just for this album!
何だって！？
What?!
そしてさらに！なんかまだ未発表の楽曲もあるとかないとか...
And furthermore! There may or may not be some unreleased tracks too...
え！？え！？ないとか、あるとか！？
Eh?! Eh?! Not there, or are they?!
何曲！？8か9か10か11か...多すぎる、多すぎる！
How many songs?! 8 or 9 or 10 or 11... that's too many!
ということでですね、通常盤になるんですけども、あ、ちょっと上が見えないで...
So, this is the standard edition, but oh, I can't see the top...
早い、早い！流れがね、早い。
It's too fast! The slides are moving too fast.
通常盤には初回限定特典があります！
The standard edition comes with a first-press limited bonus!
こちらですね。各メンバーのソロバージョン、そしてジャケット4種類のうちランダムで1枚付きます。
It's this. It includes a solo version for each member, and one of four random jackets.
そしてこちらですね、4枚並べるとどうやら一枚絵になるとのことですよ！
And this, apparently if you line all four up, they form a single picture!
え、すごい！繋がりそうな顔してる！
Eh, amazing! They do look like they'd connect!
ラッちゃんのツノが刀の上にある！
La-chan's horn is right on top of the sword!
本当だ。あ、じゃあこれさ、ね、並べないと。
It's true. Oh, then we definitely have to line them up.
並べないとね！並べないといけない！
Gotta line them up! We absolutely must!
そして！完全生産限定盤封入特典は...
And! The bonus for the complete limited edition is...
かっこよさ満点の今回のアルバムには、holoXらしい秘密の仕掛けが！
This super cool album has a secret gimmick typical of holoX!
秘密の仕掛け！？え、我々も分かってないぞ！？
A secret gimmick?! Wait, even we don't know about it?!
隠されているとか...何だって！？
It's hidden... what did you say?!
はい、ちょっと私たちも分からないのですが...この後22時から販売開始です！
Yes, we don't really know either, but... sales start tonight at 22:00!
今夜22時から！
Tonight from 22:00!
ぜひぜひご予約お願いいたします！
Please, please make your pre-orders!
ということで、めっちゃ告知盛りだくさんだったんですけど...
So, that was a lot of announcements, but...
はい、まあね、この告知カードちゃんたちはこれで役目も終わりということで。
Yes, well, these announcement cards have finished their job now.
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!
それで消せんの？
You can erase them like that?
お金かけすぎだろ！このギミックやばいだろ！
You're spending too much on effects! This gimmick is crazy!
これで消えたはず...一瞬だけね。
They should be gone now... just for a moment.
holoXの力ってすげーんだからみんな！
The power of holoX is amazing, everyone!
はい、ということで、ライブもラストスパートでございます！
Yes, and with that, the live show is entering its final spurt!
この後ですね、何やら...お知らせ？サプライズ？があるらしいですよ。
After this, it seems like... there's an announcement? Or a surprise?
何々！？
What is it?!
はい、最後までチャンネルはそのままでお願いいたします！
Yes, please stay tuned to the channel until the very end!
最後まで楽しんで、行くぞー！
Enjoy until the end! Let's go!
行くぞー！
Let's go!
1, 2!
1, 2, 3, 4!
holoX!
そこに跪け
Kneel before me!
High-stay the world. Everything is mine.
一刀両断 叩き斬れ
Cut them down with a single stroke!
終わりなき輪廻に 迷いし子らよ
O children lost in the endless cycle of rebirth,
漆黒の翼で 誘おう
I shall invite you with pitch-black wings.
我ら エデンの星を統べる者
We are the rulers of the Star of Eden.
秘密結社 holoX
Secret Society holoX
参上 でござる！
Has arrived!
Woah, woah, woah...
反論 どうしようもない この世界
There's no point in arguing with this world.
同情 してほしい
I want some sympathy.
晩鐘 終末 告げる鐘が鳴る
The evening bell, announcing the end, is ringing.
Wah-pah-pah... down the West
Sing a song of ink and magic
心地良いことだけが 全て
Only pleasant things are everything.
堕ちてゆく 闇の底へ
Falling to the bottom of the darkness.
Sweet, sweet melody. Hold on, go, go.
手の鳴る方へ
Follow the sound of the clapping hands.
もう逃げられない
You can't escape anymore.
ほら 闇に染まれば
Look, if you're stained with darkness...
世界を塗り替えろ
Repaint the world!
望めば呉れてやろう 全て
I'll give you everything if you wish for it.
常識 破り捨てろ
Throw away common sense!
狂い 狂い 倒せ
Go mad, go mad, and strike them down!
火をつけろ
Light the fire!
Wah-pah-pah-pah
全てを喰らい尽くせ
Devour everything!
Wah-pah-pah-pah
秘密を教えてやろう
I'll tell you the secret.
Woah, woah, woah...
悪のカリスマ 導くぞ 溜め息さ
I'll lead you, the charisma of evil, it's a sigh.
正義とか 知らないし 地ならしして いざない
I don't know about justice, I'll level the ground and invite you.
真面目に不真面目 礼賛の通過儀礼
Seriously unserious, a rite of passage for praise.
望み求め 願い叶え 世界征服
Seeking desire, fulfilling wishes, world domination!
Wah-pah-pah... down the West
Sing a song of ink and magic
退屈な世界に バイバイバイ
Bye-bye-bye to this boring world.
覚めることのない夢を見せる
I'll show you a dream you'll never wake up from.
ほら お眠みなさい
Now, go to sleep.
もっと もっと 遠くへ
Further, even further.
Hold on, go, go. 行きたいでしょう？
Hold on, go, go. You want to go, right?
もうやめられない
You can't stop now.
ほら 悪に染まれば
Look, if you're stained with evil...
世界を塗り替えろ
Repaint the world!
望むもの与えよう 全て
I'll give you everything you wish for.
ルールを書き換えろ
Rewrite the rules!
グルグル回し尽くせ 焼き尽くせ
Keep spinning around, burn it all down!
Wah-pah-pah-pah
全てをまがい物へ
Turn everything into fakes!
Wah-pah-pah-pah
秘密を教えてやろう
I'll tell you the secret.
ついに4周年
Finally, the 4th anniversary!
狂気の宴の始まりだ
It's the beginning of the feast of madness!
貴様ら 準備はいいか？
Are you guys ready?
Oh!
刮目せよ！
Witness this!
holoX, holoX!
手を挙げろ、手を挙げろ！
Hands up, hands up!
いろは、いろは！
Iroha, Iroha!
叫ぶでござる！
I'm going to scream!
こより、こより！
Koyori, Koyori!
踊って、踊って！
Dance, dance!
世界を征服 holoX!
Conquering the world, holoX!
世界を変えてく holoX!
Changing the world, holoX!
ルイ姉、ルイ姉！
Lui-nee, Lui-nee!
もっと、もっと！
More, more!
ラプラス、ラプラス！
La+, La+!
最後は全員で！
At last, everyone together!
holoX, holoX!
世界を手にする holoX!
Taking the world, holoX!
世界を変えてく holoX!
Changing the world, holoX!
世界をこの手に holoX!
Taking the world in our hands, holoX!
Ah!
心を解き放て
Set your heart free.
Hold on, go, go. 身をまかせて
Hold on, go, go. Give yourself over to it.
もう逃げられない
You can't escape anymore.
ほら 闇に染まれば
Look, if you're stained with darkness...
世界を塗り替えろ
Repaint the world!
望めば呉れてやろう 全て
I'll give you everything if you wish for it.
常識 破り捨てろ
Throw away common sense!
クルクル抜いたおせ 火をつけろ
Keep spinning them over, light the fire!
Wah-pah-pah-pah
全てを喰らい尽くせ
Devour everything!
Wah-pah-pah-pah
秘密を教えてやろう
I'll tell you the secret.
Woah, woah, woah...
「我らエデンの星を統べる者、秘密結社...」
"We who rule the Planet of Eden, Secret Society..."
「holoX!」「でござる〜！」
"holoX!" "De-gozaru~!"
Let's go!
「機は熟した！
"The time is ripe!
暁闇より現れし英霊たちよ、
O heroic spirits emerging from the dawn,
準備はいいか！」
are you ready?"
「あ〜〜〜！！！」
"Ahhhhh!!!"
Are you ready?
ラッパッパ LaPaLaPa ラッパッパ
LaPaTa LaPaTa ラッパッパ
Ra-pa-pa La-Pa-La-Pa Ra-pa-pa
La-Pa-Ta La-Pa-Ta Ra-pa-pa
ラッパッパ LaPaLaPa ラッパッパ
LaPaTa LaPaTa ラッパッパ
Ra-pa-pa La-Pa-La-Pa Ra-pa-pa
La-Pa-Ta La-Pa-Ta Ra-pa-pa
夜が深まる ほらダークネス
Night deepens, look, it's Darkness
能ある鷹はPONで隠そう
A capable hawk hides it with clumsiness
脳に従えエゴイスティック
Obey your brain, egoistic
のっと！ニンニン！！サムライDJ
Not! Nin-nin!! Samurai DJ
闇金しないけど フルベッドでしょ
No loan sharking, but a full bet, right?
シャキン！シャキン！
Shakin! Shakin!
征服すればOK 切り裂く赤字
If we conquer, it's OK; slicing the deficit
シャキン！シャキン！
Shakin! Shakin!
悪の手のひら 踊りたくなる
In the palm of evil, you'll want to dance
ほら君も 気づけば ノリノリです
Look, before you know it, you're in the groove
どうしようもない Don't show, No mine
堕ちてく運命
It can't be helped, Don't show, No mine
A fate that falls away
ならしょうがない もう全部 塗り替えよう
Then it can't be helped, let's repaint it all
XとXとXとXが 交差する真ん中で
Where X and X and X and X intersect, right in the center
NextとNextとNextと世界はもう始まって
With Next and Next and Next, the world has already begun
(ウォオオオ オーオーオー) 飛びな 飛びな
(Woah oh oh oh oh) Fly, fly away
闇が呼ぶ方へ (ウォオオオ オーオーオー)
Towards where the darkness calls (Woah oh oh oh oh)
暗黒のエクスデス
Darkness Ex-Death
「混沌としたこの世界を我らholoX色に塗り替えるのだ！
"We shall repaint this chaotic world in the colors of holoX!
皆の者、かかれ！」
Everyone, at them!"
「Yes My Dark!!!」
"Yes My Dark!!!"
「完璧漆黒（アブソリュート・ダークネス・インフィニティ）！
"Absolute Darkness Infinity!
エデンの星は我が手中に！」
The Planet of Eden is in my hands!"
「魔眼ホークアイ！」
"Magic Eye Hawkeye!"
「お前もホロクサーの一員となるのだ！」
"You too shall become a member of the holoXers!"
「カヤリニウムボンバー！」
"Koyorinium Bomber!"
「これで君も、コヨリメロメロ〜！」
"Now you too are head over heels for Koyori~!"
「一颯木っ端微塵！
"Iroha-style Smash! To smithereens!
一刀両断叩き切れ！」
Slash them in two!"
どうしようもない Don't show, No mine
堕ちてく運命
It can't be helped, Don't show, No mine
A fate that falls away
ならしょうがない もう全部 塗り替えよう
Then it can't be helped, let's repaint it all
「刮目せよ！！」
"Watch closely!!"
XとXとXとXが 交差する真ん中で
Where X and X and X and X intersect, right in the center
NextとNextとNextと世界はもう始まって
With Next and Next and Next, the world has already begun
(ウォオオオ オーオーオー) 飛びな 飛びな
(Woah oh oh oh oh) Fly, fly away
隅までサイダーに (ウォオオオ オーオーオー)
Cider to every corner (Woah oh oh oh oh)
笑うのは holoXです
The ones laughing will be holoX
ラッパッパ LaPaLaPa ラッパッパ
LaPaTa LaPaTa ラッパッパ
Ra-pa-pa La-Pa-La-Pa Ra-pa-pa
La-Pa-Ta La-Pa-Ta Ra-pa-pa
ラッパッパ LaPaLaPa ラッパッパ
LaPaTa LaPaTa ラッパッパ
Ra-pa-pa La-Pa-La-Pa Ra-pa-pa
La-Pa-Ta La-Pa-Ta Ra-pa-pa
Yeah!!!
機ハ熟シター
The time has ripened
全テノ "holoXer" ヘ告グー
To all "holoXers"
集ヘ、決戦ノ地ー
Gather at the site of the final battle
2026.4.29
PIA ARENA MM
秘密結社holoX Live 2026 MISSION
ファーストミッション
Secret Society holoX Live 2026 MISSION
First Mission
世界ヲ手ニスル 準備ハイイカ
Are you ready to take the world?
狂気ノ宴ノハジマリダ
The banquet of madness begins
やった〜！！
We did it!!
「みんな驚いてくれてる！」
"Everyone is surprised!"
「いかがでしたか？」
"How was it?"
「すごい！やばいね！」
"Amazing! This is crazy!"
「ということで」
"So..."
「なんと我々の現地ライブが決まりました！」
"Unbelievably, our live concert has been decided!"
「やった〜！ありがとうございます！」
"Yay! Thank you so much!"
「ファーストミッションや！ピアアリーナ！」
"First Mission! Pia Arena!"
「ということで、みんなそれぞれね、感想と、ライブに向けて抱負をお願いしたいと思います」
"So, I'd like everyone to share their thoughts and aspirations for the live concert."
んー、まずは、じゃあ私から。
Mmm, first, well, let's start with me.
はい！
Okay!
決まったな、本当に。
It's really happening.
決まったね。
It is.
いや、めちゃくちゃね、あの、デビューの時から、ライブやりたいねって言ってて。
Ever since our debut, we've been saying we wanted to do a live show.
デビュー前から。
Even before we debuted.
それがもうありがたいことに...
And now, thankfully...
みんなの協力のおかげで、ホロクサーさんたちの応援のおかげで...
Thanks to everyone's cooperation and the support of the holoxers...
叶いました！やったー！
It’s finally coming true! We did it!
やったー！ありがとうございます！
Yay! Thank you so much!
ホロックスのみんなで当日は盛り上げたいと思いますので。
The whole holoX team is going to make the big day a blast.
ぜひみんな遊びに来てください。かっこいいホロックスを見に来てね！
Please come and visit us. Come and see the cool holoX!
ということで、続いては、じゃあ、こよ！
And with that, next up is... Koyo!
はい！
Yes!
えー、まぁ今言ってた通り、みんなライブやりたいねって話もしてたし。
As she said, we've all talked about wanting to do a live show.
やっぱり、こよは、一番忘れられない風景が、初めてのフェスで、ホロックスでやった時の...
For me, the most unforgettable sight was performing together at our first festival...
あの「ジョイペイント」で会場がもうワッてなってくれたのを浴びた時...
When the crowd went wild during 'Zoy Paint'...
あれをもうずっと忘れられないんで。
I'll never forget that moment.
やっぱりその、今度はホロクサーさんたちだけの会場...
So, this time, having a venue just for holoxers...
俺たちの会場でやれるわけじゃないですか。めちゃくちゃ嬉しいです。
Our very own venue. I'm just so incredibly happy.
そして、やらせてくれることに、してくれた大人の皆さんにも、ありがとうございます。
And I want to thank the staff for making this happen.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
この4人のできる力を全て出して、歌とダンスもね、より一層力を込めてやっていきますので。
We'll give it our all, focusing even more on our singing and dancing.
絶対現地、そして、来られない人は映像でも絶対見に来てください！よろしくお願いします！
Please come see us in person, or watch the stream if you can't be there! Thank you!
お願いします！
Please!
はい！いろはし！
Okay! Irohashi!
はい！
Yes!
みんな！生でござるたちの声が聞ける機会、ホロックスのこのハーモニーが聞ける機会...
Everyone! This is your chance to hear our voices live and witness the holoX harmony...
叫び声、俺たちの共鳴、共鳴が聞ける機会、来たぞ！
The shouts, our resonance... the chance to hear that resonance has finally come!
いやもう本当にね、ホロックスやっぱりみんな言ってるけど、デビュー前から単独ライブをこのメンバーでやりたいってずっと言っていたので。
As we've all been saying, we've wanted to do a solo live with this group since before we even debuted.
それがやっと叶ってね、デカイ声出して、みんなで盛り上がれるのを、今か今かと楽しみにしています。
It's finally coming true. I can't wait for us all to raise our voices and have a blast together.
我々も4人とも、しっかり当日までレッスンや、練習も、パフォーマンスも全部みんなに楽しんでもらえることいっぱい考えて挑みますので。
All four of us will be working hard on our lessons and rehearsals, thinking of everything to make sure you have a great time.
見ている皆さんも、ぜひ、全力で楽しみにして、そして当日は楽しんでください！頑張ります！
So please, look forward to it with everything you've got and enjoy the day! I'll do my best!
盛り上げる準備できてます！頑張るぞー！
I'm ready to rock! Let's do this!
じゃあ最後、ラプ様、ビシッと決めてくれ！
Alright, last but not least, Laplus, wrap it up for us!
いやちょっと毎回この最後やめてほしいんだよな。しゃあないけど。
Man, I really wish you'd stop making me go last every time. Well, whatever.
ちょっ、みんな、ついにホロックスが、俺たちが、ライブ！
Everyone, holoX is finally... we are finally having a live show!
もうみんなはさ、もうすごいライブやりたい、音楽大好き、みたいなのずっと聞いてたからさ。
I've always heard how much everyone wanted to do a live show and how much they love music.
俺は嬉しいよ。
I'm just so happy for them.
いやもちろん当事者よ。
Wait, you're one of them too!
あの、やっぱりライブが一番楽しいから。みんなでやってる。
Because, performing live is the most fun thing of all. Doing it together.
やっぱホロックスの活動ってなんかライブって感じじゃん。
I feel like holoX is really defined by its live performances.
だからそれがさ、俺たちだけで、しかもホロクサーがバッていいるところでできるのが嬉しいよな。
So being able to do it with just us, in front of all those holoxers, makes me so happy.
以上に熱いや。熱い。いやー本当に俺たち色々あったけど。
It's so emotional. Truly. We've really been through a lot.
これからも本当に4人いれば大丈夫だから。頑張ろう。
As long as the four of us are together, everything will be fine. Let's do our best.
一致団結して！頑張るぞー！やったー！
United as one! Let's do it! Yeah!
速報です！トレンド1位ということで！
Breaking news! We're number one on trending!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
ここから4月29日までもう止まらねえぞ、予定に入れまくっておいてください！
We're not stopping until April 29th, so make sure to mark your calendars!
秘密結社holoX 1st ライブ「First Mission」は、4月29日、ぴあアリーナMMにて開催されます！
Secret Society holoX's 1st Live 'First Mission' will be held at Pia Arena MM on April 29th!
あけておけ！あけておいて！
Keep the day free! Keep it open!
秘密結社holoX 1st LIVE 2026
「First Mission」
ファーストミッション
Secret Society holoX 1st LIVE 2026
'First Mission'
2026. 4. 29 Wed. PIA ARENA MM
#SSholoX世界リペイント計画
#SSholoXWorldRepaintProject
諸々の詳細は後日発表予定とのことなので、皆さん続報を待つでござる！よろしく！
More details will be announced later, so stay tuned for more news! We're counting on you!
そしてそして先ほど聞いていただきました新曲、「共鳴X」です。聞いていただきましたけれども...
And just now, you heard our new song, 'Kyomei X'. You've just heard it, but...
22時10分よりですね、
Starting from 22:10,
MVをプレミア公開したいと思います！
we will be having an MV premiere!
このあと、MVプレミア公開
Coming up: MV Premiere
イェーイ！
Yay!
『暁闇エクスタシス』！
"Gyoyo Ecstasy"!
おっしゃれーですね。
So stylish.
かっこいいね！
It's cool!
そして本日24時ですね、
And, at midnight today,
12月2日の0時にデジタルリリースが開始されますので、
the digital release will start at 0:00 on December 2nd,
ライブに向けて、たくさん聴いてくれよな！
so listen to it a lot for the live!
いや、もうコールできるとこいっぱいだからね！
Yeah, there are so many parts for calls!
めちゃめちゃ、もうライブのための曲！
It's totally a song made for live events!
エクスト！エクスト！エクスト！
Exto! Exto! Exto!
お前ら新曲いっぱい聴いて、
You guys, listen to the new songs a lot,
予習して、ライブ楽しみにしててほしい！
practice, and look forward to the live!
そして、アルバム『シークレット・オーダー』を持って...
And, with the album "Secret Order"...
持って？持って？持って？
With? With? With?
忘れないように気をつけて持ってライブ来てね！
Be careful not to forget it and bring it to the live!
持って、持って、持ってね！
Bring it, bring it, okay?!
聴いて予習してね！
Listen and practice!
アルバムは、えーと、22時から販売開始です！
The album sales will start at 22:00!
もう1分ないよ！早い！
Less than a minute left! So soon!
ホロックスを、みんな、
To everyone in holoX,
え、本当に、4年間ありがとう！
um, really, thank you for the 4 years!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
来年はもう、ホロックスの、我々の年にしていくので、頑張ろうね！
We're going to make next year holoX's year, our year, so let's do our best!
5年目も、よろしくお願いします！
Please support us in our 5th year too!
よろしくお願いしまーす！
Please do!
じゃあみんな、せーので行くよ！
Now everyone, on three!
せーの！
One, two!
バイバーイ！改散！改散！改散！改散！
Bye-bye! Dismissed! Dismissed! Dismissed! Dismissed!
やったー！やったー！やったー！やったー！
We did it! We did it! We did it! We did it!
4周年をお祝いしてくれてありがとう！これからもよろしくね！大好きです♡ (高嶺ルイ)
Thank you for celebrating our 4th anniversary! Please keep supporting us! I love you! ♡ (Takane Lui)
LIVEはどうだった？忘れたくないくらい最高の思い出をありがとう！ (ラプラス・ダークネス)
How was the LIVE? Thank you for the best memories that I never want to forget! (Laplus Darknesss)
4周年まで一緒にいてくれてありがとう！！みんなのことが大好きです！！これからもずっとそばにいてね (沙花叉クロヱ)
Thank you for being with us until our 4th anniversary!! I love you all!! Please stay by my side forever. (Sakamata Chloe)
holoXを、koyoriを支えてくれてありがとう！！最高の5人でお届けしました！また会おうね！！ (博衣こより)
Thank you for supporting holoX and Koyori!! We delivered this as the best five! See you again!! (Hakui Koyori)
いつも応援ありがとうございます！5年目も突っ走っていくのでついてきてください！でござる！ (風真いろは)
Thank you for your constant support! We'll keep rushing through our 5th year, so please follow us! de-gozaru! (Kazama Iroha)